Okay, smile.
If you're still having trouble with it, just fake it.
Just fake it?
That's right.
Just pretend so you know what it's like.
All right, Master.
How was this?
That's not what I had in mind!
What's going on in here?
I'm trying to teach Icarus how to smile.
How to smile, huh?
Well, you know, she's always going on about how she wants to act more human.
I thought the first logical step is to learn how to smile.
Thing is, you don't have to really be happy to pull off a smile.
It's perfectly cool to fake one if you're not feeling it.
Watch me, I'll show you.
See?
Smiling.
No!
You can't just say it!
Now try it again!
Grinning.
Damn it, Icarus!
You're just saying the words, not making the face!
I came here with one goal in mind.
To take Alpha back, but...
I can't hear my heart, but...
I can't hear my heart.
I can't hear alone.
What kind of gucken?
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm so nervous, but I'm so nervous.
I'm nervous, but I'm nervous.
I can't hear my heart, but I'm not able to stop.
Don't happen to I'm nervous.
Can you hear my heart?
Who started the music to begin?
We didn't get it.
Mr. Kaleheri.
There's nothing wrong, and you'll never know what it is.
During the Age of Exploration, the Europeans discovered the New World and embarked on a policy of colonialism,
which then turned into all-out global expansion.
Believe it or not, even Japan felt the effects.
As such, a number of Japanese were treated like slaves and sent to Europe against their will.
Toyotomi Hideyoshi, the ruler at the time, saw this trend and exiled the Jesuits from the country.
This is considered to be the beginning of Japan's isolationist era.
The slave trade was hidden beneath the flashy facade that was pushed by Western diplomats.
These marauding expansionists were indifferent to the people, leading them like cattle to slaughter in order to satisfy their own petty desires.
It's likely that within the New World hovering above us, there exists a new breed of slavery,
one which seeks to fulfill their own inhabitants' unearthly desires.
Huh? You don't know how to smile.
Yeah, right? Go figure. You'd think it would be easy for her.
Got any ideas how we could teach her?
Hmm, that's a tough one, because smiling is something we do unconsciously.
Oh, I know. Icarus. Try raising your arms above your head.
Above my head, like this.
Bunzai!
This is one of your tickle zones. It should put a big smile on your face. Doesn't it make you want to giggle?
What the? What the heck is wrong with her?
Looks like it tickled her.
But it's not the reaction I was hoping for.
Because you were doing it wrong.
Listen, tickling is an art form. Take a lesson from the master.
This is the proper technique.
Goochie, goochie, goochie, goo!
Now this should tickle.
Tomo! Okay, Tomo, that's enough!
You just stopped now!
Oh, this is gonna suck.
Quit molesting me, you pervert!
I'm confused. I don't know what it's going to take to make myself smile.
Hey, I know.
What? You don't know how to smile?
I was thinking maybe you could give her some advice.
Gee, Mr. Takaharo, weird much?
Yeah, right?
I guess there's no point in asking someone who never smiles himself.
Come on, let's go, Alpha.
Is there anything I haven't tried?
Eats me.
Well, what do we have here?
My favorite angeloids, Icarus and Nymph.
So, you want to learn how to smile?
Yes, I'm having a hard time.
So, is there a specific time of day you like to smile, or is there any advice you could give us?
Let's see.
Something that always brings a smile to my face is hitting someone as hard as I can, using a huge fly swatter.
Do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do.
It's not dead! I found a bug!
No!
Tomoki?
Now that was funny as hell.
I don't believe you.
How could you do that?
I'm sorry.
Oh, please, Tomoki.
It's not like you're going to die or anything.
Who really cares?
I really cares.
Icarus is a very impressionable person.
So did beating the crap out of Tomoki get you any closer to smiling?
Unfortunately, no.
Not yet, at least.
Oh, right.
I nearly forgot what time of year it is.
It's almost Christmas.
Oh, I know.
Why don't we all get together this weekend and throw a huge Christmas party at Tomoki's place?
It would be so much fun.
Huh?
But we all have to pitch in for it to work.
Throw the best bash ever and Icarus has to smile.
Not bad.
That sounds like a plan.
You game, Tomoki?
What do you say?
I could get my mom to bake one of her awesome cakes for us and we could put up a bunch of decorations and swap presents?
Uh, sure.
I guess that's okay.
All right, then.
This Sunday, consider it a date, okay?
What's wrong?
Why can't I smile?
It is weird.
I mean, I took off your emotional protections a while ago.
But you have to remember you were created for combat.
Maybe you're just physically incapable of it.
I was created as a combat-only model?
Well, smiling's pretty simple once you get down to it.
I wouldn't stress too much.
It's not simple.
I mean, I don't think I can even remember the last time I saw you smile.
What?
What are you trying to get at?
You haven't seemed happy for a while.
Really, it's not like you, to go this much time without smiling.
It's been too long.
It's true, yeah.
Angeloids are not designed for smiling.
Not unless we have humans around who are willing to help us learn.
And there's something else.
Lately, I've been doing a lot of worrying.
More so than normal.
But the part that's troubling me the most
is I don't know why I'm worrying.
Everything will be okay.
We'll just nip this problem in the bud.
Let's brainstorm.
I'm sure we can find a way to make you smile.
Sound good?
Sure.
Oh, holy crap.
I am so hungry.
Morning!
How's it going?
Hi.
Master.
Good morning.
Relax.
Easy, Tomaki.
Calm down.
She has wings for crying out loud.
Wings!
Is something bothering you, Master?
What?
No!
I mean, your boobs are freaking awesome.
I mean, what the heck am I saying?
Must control myself.
You're blushing, Master.
Huh?
Me?
Wait.
What the hell is going on?
What happened to your face?
It's frozen.
Dang, it didn't work.
We spent all last night putting blue on our faces
to freeze our expressions for nothing.
You guys are out of your damn minds.
Come on, let's go wash that crap off.
Don't think I didn't see that smile on your face,
because I did.
Oh, shut the hell up.
Ever since the accident, I feel like you're afraid to smile.
I... I know.
What if I took you on a date?
We could do something simple, like take a drive...
What is that all about?
A date?
Hmm?
Hey, Tomaki.
I have a great idea.
Huh?
We should all go out on a date.
What?
Sure.
So, um, do you even understand what a date is?
Because most of the time,
it's something that a boy and a girl do together by themselves.
You mean we can't do it with three people?
Oh, we can, but it's not normal.
Then who cares?
Don't you remember what Zohara said?
If we do something fun,
then the chances of Alpha cracking a smile go way up.
She needs this.
What are we waiting for?
Let's do it.
A date with Master?
What is this feeling?
Am I actually excited?
Aw, screw it.
Come on, ladies.
Let's get this threesome on the road.
Yeah, so what do we do on a date?
Oh, man, there's tons of things you can do.
That's actually a really good question,
which I don't have the answer to.
Face it, Tomaki Sakurai.
We've never been popular with the ladies.
You can't let them know this is your first real date.
Do not screw this up.
Give me that.
I gotta see.
Try taking her shopping.
If you buy her something she wants,
her impression of you will be very positive
and may lead to future intimacy.
Okay, my ladies.
Anything you want, I'll buy it for you.
Geez, Christmas really snuck up on me this year.
Better start thinking of gift ideas.
For myself, of course.
Master, I bought something.
Did you buy out the entire freaking grocery store?
What about you, Nymph?
Isn't there anything you want to buy?
Figured you'd be all about it.
Yeah, I thought about it,
but I think I'm good.
And anyways,
it wouldn't really mean much,
but thanks, though.
Hmm.
After shopping,
you can relax in a nice movie.
Try to pick a sappy one
for optimum emotional impact.
Bunch of stuff playing.
What looks good to you guys?
How about this one?
No freaking way.
Why not?
It looks right up your alley.
This one looks interesting.
Okay.
Big snail and the uvi man.
What else is there?
If a movie's not your style
and depending on your budget,
you might try an amusement park.
The mascots are not a threat to us!
Maybe this wasn't the best place
to start.
Let's check out some rides instead.
Whoa!
Master is having fun.
The world's spinning so fast,
I think my brain's gonna fly out of my ears!
That was a huge mistake.
Whoa, are you okay?
I'm having fun on my date with Master.
But still, something is missing.
You pathetic, baby.
Come on, let's get going.
There's more fun to be had.
Suck it up, Tomoki.
I'm having fun on my date with Master.
Initiating scan.
All systems read zero damage.
No faults in the organic structure.
No reactor anomalies.
All systems green.
What was that just now?
It was almost like a quick twinge of pain in my reactor.
Wow, they're amazing!
Oh, good.
She's finally chilling out a bit.
I'm gonna go see if I can find some tea or something.
You guys take your time.
I'll be back in a few minutes.
I wish Tomoki were my master.
But he's not.
Hey, Alpha.
I don't understand this place.
Why are all the animals in cages?
I don't know.
Here's what I'm thinking.
Maybe this cage is kinda like the chokers we wear.
If that's true, they want out.
Wouldn't you agree, Alpha?
If these animals could leave their cages and roam free,
think about how much happier they'd be.
What?
You know, Tomoki does so much for us.
Would it make him happy if we set them loose?
I don't know, would he?
Master would be thrilled.
Alpha!
What is this?
What are you doing?
Master would be...
Happy.
So happy.
Gotta love peace and quiet.
There's nothing better.
No!
Why do I get the feeling my date has something to do with this?
Hey!
Get back here!
This is your fault!
Master would be...
So happy.
Calm down!
Don't panic!
We'll return the animals to the sea.
We'll return the animals to our home.
What are you doing?
Hey, get back here! This is your fault!
Master would be so happy.
Calm down! Don't panic!
We'll return the animals to their cages!
Hello, police! We have a naked man running around the park tampering with all the cages!
All units proceed to the scene immediately. We have multiple dangerous animals on the loose.
Must be some new kind of terrorism. Everyone on high alert.
The little bastard's playing with us!
Dammit! Really pour it on, boys! We're taking back the peace!
Earlier today, a nude man wreaked havoc on the city zoo, sending the patrons and staff into a frenzy.
I always assumed he'd end up doing something like this, though he was actually a really nice guy.
If it were me, I'd give him the frickin' death penalty.
I missed it!
I am very sorry about all of this, Master.
I'm done with this crap day! I want to go home!
We did plenty of date stuff, let's call it!
No way! There's so many other things we want to do!
You want to do more? Like what?
Are you insane?
It says right here, if the date goes well, you're supposed to kiss each other at the end.
Yeah, if it goes well, and you're only supposed to kiss one person, not two!
Oh.
So only one of us will get a kiss.
Hey, Alva?
You mind if I try it?
That's okay, isn't it?
Wait, listen to me, both of you!
Tomoki?
Hey! Hold on, where are you going?
You can't just leave me here alone with her!
Crap, what should I do?
No, wait! Stop! I was just kidding!
Geez, I can't believe you fell for it!
What is this feeling?
Is it because I'm thinking of Tomoki?
It's so strange.
Are you okay?
Nymph?
It's nothing! My reactor's just acting a little weird!
Keep your paws off me, creepo!
Why'd you have to hit me?
I've done... something horrible.
Excuse me?
Hey, wait!
Wait!
I'm so sorry, Alva.
All I wanted was to make some memories for myself before it was too late.
But I realized that I have enough.
Reactor scan. Functioning at 100%.
The time I've spent with you two has been amazing.
Sure, it was short, but so sweet.
And don't worry, Alpha.
Even if you can't smile, as long as Tomoki is your master, he'll care about you more and more each day.
Forever.
My reactor must be damaged.
It hurts.
What is with you?
You up and fly away and you come back totally filthy.
I'm sorry, master.
And Nymph ran off pouting too.
What the hell is going on today?
Today was when I went on my first date and wasn't even able to smile.
Come on, let's go home.
Rules say the date doesn't end until I drop you off.
All right.
It looks like you're free to roam now.
Glad to see it.
So long, you guys. Tomoki, Alpha.
the star is high.
If you want to be that star is no83.
Until we leave as a star, this guy will go back and leave.
What's the only being that star is there?
Can I leave for you and let the star begin one for ya?
The star is there?
Peace out.
If you don't have one in the midswhere,
with a star thatchuckles into fruitSHOW after you want with.
The star is the star, I be doing the star floor there.
You may be so proud.
Let me give you this flower
The red flower, the red flower
To that person's hair
Will it go the same place before light?
The rainbow is true
Some of your land.
Alright then, where should I go?
The sea?
Or maybe a deserted spot in the mountains?
I'm sure as long as I go somewhere quiet and disappear, no one will notice I'm gone.
Or maybe it would be funny if I headed back to the synapse with, oh, I don't know, a bomb or something like that.
Wonder what Master would think of me then.
It's Kama!
Next time, Queen of the Sky.